In this assignment,
you're gonna explore the use of
the JavaScript methods in
order to control the models.
Earlier when we implemented the models,
we used the data attributes in
order to trigger the showing and
hiding of the model.
We can replace that with
JavaScript methods for
the model that enables us to show and
hide their models.
Going to the web page, now,
when you click on the Log in button,
you're gonna see the Log in model
being displayed on the screen.
Similarly, when you click
on the Result button,
you'll still see the Reserve Table
model being shown on the screen there.
Now, both of these now are triggered
using the JavaScript methods
rather than using the data attributes.
So in this assignment, you're gonna
remove the data attributes that you were
using to trigger the models, and instead,
replace them with JavaScript methods