[SOUND] Let us now see how we can set up
Node.js and NPM on our computer.
First, go to nodejs.org, and then, on the
webpage you will see a download button.
Click on the download button to download
the Node.js installer to your computer.
Once you have downloaded,
then double-click on the installer to
start installing Node.js on your machine.
I have double-clicked on
the Node.js installer on my Mac and
then I see this installer window open up.
If you are using Windows or
Linux, you might see a slightly
different configuration of the window.
You can go ahead and
continue the installation following
the instructions on the screen.
Once you have completed the installation
then you can close the installed window.
Once you complete the installation,
in order to verify the node has been
correctly installed on your machine,
open up a terminal window if
you're using a Mac or Linux, or
the command window or
the PowerShell if you're using Windows.
At the prompt, type in node -V to
check the version of node that has
been installed on your machine.
Similarly, you can type in npm
-v to check the version of
npm that has been
installed on your machine.
If both of these work correctly, and
the version number is indicated,
then your machine is all set up and
ready to use Node.js.