As we come to the conclusion of
this course, I hope that you
had a good time going through
the materials in this course.
I hope you have gotten a good grasp
of Bootstrap and its capabilities.
So in this course, we examined
Bootstrap in sufficient detail,
we looked at responsive web design and
the use of Bootstrap Grid System
to construct responsive websites.
We also looked at Bootstrap CSS and
JavaScript components.
Finally, we looked at Web Tools.
We looked at Node.js and NPM, and Bower.
As we conclude this course and move onto
the next course where we will look at
JavaScript based frameworks,
in particular AngularJS in more detail.
I hope to see you around
in the next course.